<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Instagram.hk.cn</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>orangemonkey001@outlook (instagram.hk.cn)</managingEditor>
      <webMaster>orangemonkey001@outlook (instagram.hk.cn)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 17:48:21 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
  <title>28 Years Later Sequel In Development With Original Writer &amp; Director, New Trilogy Planned</title>
  <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/28-years-later-sequel-in-development-with-original-writer-director-new-trilogy-planned/</link>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 17:48:21 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>instagram.hk.cn</author>
  <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/28-years-later-sequel-in-development-with-original-writer-director-new-trilogy-planned/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[A 28 Days Later sequel titled 28 Years Later is in development from original writer Alex Garland and director Danny Boyle with a new trilogy planned.
SUMMARY Director Danny Boyle and writer Alex Garland are reuniting for a new 28 Days Later sequel, titled 28 Years Later. The film is part of a planned trilogy that aims to continue the success of the original post-apocalyptic movie. 28 Days Later is credited with revitalizing the zombie genre and influencing subsequent zombie movies and TV shows.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>8 Hunger Games Character Names That Foreshadowed Their Roles In The Story</title>
  <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/8-hunger-games-character-names-that-foreshadowed-their-roles-in-the-story/</link>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 17:48:21 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>instagram.hk.cn</author>
  <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/8-hunger-games-character-names-that-foreshadowed-their-roles-in-the-story/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[The characters of The Hunger Games and Ballad of Songbirds and Snakes have prophetic names, which poetically align with their roles in the story.
SUMMARY The names in The Hunger Games franchise have symbolic meanings that foreshadow the characters&rsquo; roles and fates. The names of the characters in The Hunger Games reflect the series&rsquo; commentary on social concepts and draw inspiration from the Roman Empire. The intricate choice of names in The Hunger Games adds layers of depth and meaning to the characters and their stories.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Aquaman 2 Box Office Disappointment Continues Shocking DCEU Trend</title>
  <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/aquaman-2-box-office-disappointment-continues-shocking-dceu-trend/</link>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 17:48:21 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>instagram.hk.cn</author>
  <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/aquaman-2-box-office-disappointment-continues-shocking-dceu-trend/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[Aquaman and the Lost Kingdom&rsquo;s box office performance continues (and ultimately completes) a rather shocking trend for the DCEU as a whole.
SUMMARY Following Aquaman 2, all direct DCEU sequels have made less money than their predecessors, continuing and completing a disappointing trend. External factors, such as the pandemic and the upcoming DCU reboot, have affected overall box office performance. The DCEU&rsquo;s sequel numbers are not as bad as they appear, considering the circumstances surrounding their releases.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>New Star Trek Origin Movie Set Decades Before J.J. Abrams 2009 Film Announced</title>
  <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/new-star-trek-origin-movie-set-decades-before-j.j.-abrams-2009-film-announced/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2009 17:48:21 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>instagram.hk.cn</author>
  <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/new-star-trek-origin-movie-set-decades-before-j.j.-abrams-2009-film-announced/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[A new theatrical Star Trek movie planned to be an origin set before J.J. Abrams&rsquo; Star Trek 2009 movie taps a director and a screenwriter.
SUMMARY Paramount Pictures is developing a new Star Trek movie set &ldquo;decades before&rdquo; J.J. Abrams&rsquo; Star Trek 2009, which will serve as an origin story for the franchise. Previous attempts to make Star Trek 4 have not been successful, but it is still in &ldquo;active development&rdquo; as the final chapter of Abrams&rsquo; Star Trek saga starring Chris Pine.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
